What in the world is going on?
and one person With the
tears of tears I'm going to
to
cry
I've seen my dreams
I'm not even though I'm not even though
I'm only coming I'm
becoming the best of you
I wanted to that But when you were the time
when I was the one who was I I'm always
connected I'm always the right way to it
I'm always the right way to it I'm always
gonna go with me I'm always the right way
to the world Let's
I enjoyed celebrating spring Amid
the flowering cherry blossoms
I loved breathing in the fragrance
of fresh green leaves as I ran.
I thought we would always live our whole
lives with nature at our fingertips.
But I was wrong.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
Ha-ha-ha!
Back off!
With me, Yuki!
Our objective is complete.
We should leave Shikoku.
Why don't you head back
without me, Jouryuu?
I'm going to stay here and watch a while.
That other Shuki is pretty
strong, don't you think?
I wanna see how this all plays out.
All right, then.
Make it quick.
Focus.
I learned how to step up my game
during our training sessions.
And I have something worth fighting for!
It won't stop!
Miss Kyoka!
Here it comes!
I could even channel my
strength into my mouth!
Talk about dangerous!
I kind of like this guy!
I can see that you're extremely angry.
That's too bad.
Because my rage burns
a hundred times water!
Mechuga!
This is where you perish.
The technique I learned
to carve you into pieces.
Howling cherry blossom!
No countering or dodging me this time!
With the unyielding king of my blades!
You will die!
The time has finally come to bow down!
Miss Kyoka?
Kyoka?
She's gone.
Go gather up the others.
Got it.
This victory...
is for my hometown.
That was quite the spectacular battle.
The commander of the 7th squadron
is pretty impressive too.
But more importantly, that man.
I find him quite interesting.
Big sis are you hurt?
Just a few scratches i'll heal quickly.
Oh miss tenka hey everyone you
didn't have to come back right away!
This is a family issue
so i have to be here
you don't have to worry about the others.
Ney's doing a great job
handling the situation.
So what are you going to do now?
i can't say i feel like leading
a revolt the shuki we rallied
are gone plus they abducted coco
nan but i still have to save them
are you willing to let me protect
you if you don't plan on causing
trouble there's no need for us
to keep fighting you're a victim.
of a Mato mishap.
I'll do everything I can
to rescue your friends.
Same for me.
I want to help you too.
We won't let the Onmyo Bureau
touch you either. Big sis?
I trust Tenka and Kyoka, but I can't trust
the organization? as a whole. But why?
You can't stay here anymore!
We've got other villages, and my
friends are already on the move.
It's my job to look after them.
If they have somewhere to hide,
then choosing not to accept our
offer would be a sensible decision.
What?
Supreme Commander Yamashiro, if the Onmyo
Bureau is conducting these experiments,
there is a decent chance
she is already aware of it.
The Supreme Commander of
the Demon Defense Force.
But why does that matter?
It's reassuring to have a Supreme
Commander who's so patriotic,
but she's a little unnerving.
I couldn't bring myself to
attack Alba during our fight.
But the Supreme Commander
wouldn't have hesitated.
Whether something's right
or wrong, it doesn't matter.
That's just how she is.
Which is why hiding might actually
be a safer option at the moment.
Luckily, our conversations
haven't left this cave.
And we can investigate the Onyo Bureau.
Then, how long will my sister
and her friends have to hide?
That's an easy one. Huh?
Haine, we're back from...
You made it back home!
I'm glad you're okay.
Sorry for making you worry.
I owe everyone else for saving me.
How are Himari and the others?
They'll be cleared to come back
after two or three days of bed rest.
Good to hear.
Then I'm off to get my
injuries looked at as well.
I'll check on Himari and the
others while I'm in the area.
Thanks.
Miss Tenka! Huh?
I, uh...
The next time we're alone, I
expect a very generous reward.
I'll catch you later.
Nei has to go drop off a
change of clothes for Ms.
Himari and Ms.
Shushu.
Please feel free to unwind in the bath.
I think I'll do just that.
Yuki, stand by in your slave form.
Come get me at the
first sign of an attack.
Yes, ma 'am.
You must be hungry by now.
Are you up to eating some dinner?
Uh, sure.
Are you okay?
Are you in any pain?
No, I'm fine.
It's just, the others are...
The Demon Defense Force has
a talented medical team.
They'll bounce back soon enough.
Yeah, that's what Ms. Kyoka said.
If something happens,
it's your job to work extra hard on
behalf of everyone who's in the hospital.
So eat something when you
can, and try to cheer up!
Senpai's orders.
You got it, thanks.
It's okay, I'll go grab you some food.
Oh, take your time, and be careful.
Don't worry, I'm your senpai, remember?
I'm disengaging my ability.
Okay.
Go rinse off in the shower
before your reward begins. What?
Once you're finished, meet me in my room.
Be quick about it.
Right.
What is this?
Apparently, your reward is
sleeping in my bed with me.
Oh, alrighty then.
I know that rest is important, but...
Lack of clothing is dumb.
You're such a pervert.
Sorry about that.
You'll be exhausted if you don't get
some sleep and the reward won't end.
I feel wide awake.
Really?
Huh?
In that case, perhaps we
should do something else.
Huh?
Wait!
Sit still, trust me on this!
The price of my ability only
lets me move so far, but...
What exactly is the point of this again?
To make sure you understand
that I am your master!
Yes, yes, I am fully aware of that fact!
Except you ignored my orders!
Then obeyed your sister instead
and got yourself captured!
I'm sorry, I didn't mean to!
It was just a knee-jerk
reaction, it's an old habit!
I surrender!
You said your sister always used
to put you in a headlock rack!
You'll need extensive disciplining, but
I'll start with the same method she used!
The fact that I'm okay with
this is a little concerning.
I swear.
Now you get some rest.
Why did you bring two of them here?
For insurance.
For when the time comes that it
decides to be picky about its food.
You spoil that damn thing.
Then again, it does need food to grow.
It's the only god that ever has.
That just means it's going
to be a powerful one.
Hear that?
You get to live forever inside a god.
This seems promising.
Our newest friend.
And look, she's about to be born.
A whole feast!
To celebrate your return and as
a way of showing my gratitude,
we pulled out all the stops.
So this is one of Yuki's famous meals.
It looks and smells delicious!
We'll make ramen with the leftover broth.
Yes, please!
I can't believe you have an
appetite for something so low-brow.
Well, you're welcome to
not eat it, Yachi-ho.
Oh, no.
It's my responsibility to assess your taste
in food, no matter how disastrous it is.
Yachi, what are you talking about?
You love that kind of stuff, and you're
always sneaking snacks and sweets, silly.
Hey, guys, I think we
should, uh... Come on.
Let's raise a toast. Yeah.
Everyone grab a glass.
Oh, that's right.
You are the star this time around.
You should give a speech. Huh?
Me? Give the speech? Mm-hmm.
Uh, okay then.
Uh, I want to thank each and every
one of you for coming to save me.
It's something I'll never...
Time's up! Kanpai!
Kanpai!
Now, what should I eat first?
I mean, yeah, I can do it myself.
My food is Yuki's cooking.
It's the best.
Yeah, and they got to help out a lot, too.
Are you absolutely sure I
can't have Yuki? Shut up.
Um, guys?
That reminds me, Yuki.
We forgot to tell you something
while we were in the hospital.
Welcome home, Yuki.
I'm glad to be here.
Big Sis.
That's an easy one. Huh?
I just have to become Supreme Commander.
I'll change the Demon
Defense Forces policies.
I'll exterminate the Shuki,
protect Aoba and her friends,
and then find a way to cure them.
How does that sound?
In that case, we might finally
get to rest easy. Big Sis!
An earthquake!
The cave's collapsing!
We need to leave now! Got it!
Let's get to the exit together!
Big Sis!
Fix that for me. Huh?
Hold on!
It's all right.
I'll be watching over you.
Time's running out.
Yuki.
I swear, I will find a way to help you.
I will always fight for you.
You've gotten so strong.
You get an A+.
Thanks.
Up till now, I've been fighting
because I wanted to be a hero.
But now I have a much
more important purpose.
To cure my big sister.
That's my reason for fighting.
Good morning.
Tenka?
What are you doing in my room?
I told you, didn't I?
That I expected a generous
reward when we were alone.
I was admiring your adorable
face while you slept.
Yuki!
How long are you going to stay in bed?
Uh...
Seriously, given your recent absence,
don't you have paperwork to catch up on?
How right you are!
We'll get back to this at
a later date, okay, Yuki?
Honestly.
What? No!
Tenka was just dropping
by to say hello, I swear!
Uh...
That honestly was meant for you! Huh?
Evidently, you still don't
understand who your master is.
You need discipline.
Brace yourself.
Why are you already tired when
I just called you? Sorry, Ms.
Kyoka really put me through the ringer.
Oh?
Extra training?
Sounds like something she'd do.
What did you want to talk to me about?
I want to hone my Peach ability, too.
You mean learning, right?
I want to be an asset to the Commander.
I need to get stronger.
Which is why I need your help, Yuki.
Sure.
Be patient, Shushu.
Now is not the time to act.
Remember what you uncovered on the
internet during the hospital stay.
The art of war applies to romance, too!
Instead of vying for
attention, I need to act aloof.
According to my analysis, Yuki's
love levels look something like this.
If I don't use my brain,
I can't win the game.
It is all exactly as I envisioned it.
What is she doing?
Hey guys!
A gateway just opened up!
Get ready for battle!
What's the situation?
Currently, I'm not detecting anyone
in need of rescue near the gateway.
However, more and more
Shuki are converging.
Then we'd better hurry!
We're all counting on you. Got it? Roger!
All right, let's get...
Let's get moving, Commander.
Faster, Yugi! Right!
Kaboom!
Now! Got it!
It's time to fall down!
This is how I became...
This is the story!
Supreme Commander!
Of how I became a hero!
Coco...
Nalan...
I swear on my life I will find you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let's do it.
Oh